sooperthemes.com 2010-05-21

# Privacy | SooperThemes

## Disclaimer

Except as otherwise noted, the content of our Website ([www.sooperthemes.com](http://www.sooperthemes.com/ "www.sooperthemes.com")), including but not limited to text, graphics and icons, are copyrighted materials of Clearwind and its suppliers and affiliates, and contain trademarks, service marks and trade names of Clearwind and its suppliers and affiliates. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. You may use the content ONLY to learn about, evaluate, and/or acquire the goods or services of Clearwind.

We make every effort to provide accurate and timely information; however, there may be inadvertent technical factual inaccuracies, omissions, and typographical errors, for which we apologize. Our Website and its content are delivered on an "as-is" and "as-available" basis. Clearwind cannot ensure that files you download from our Website will be free of viruses or contamination or destructive features. Clearwind reserves the right to make changes and corrections at any time, without notice.

Should you decide to acquire goods or services from Clearwind, our online User Agreement is considered the governing agreement between both you as our customer and Clearwind, and it supercedes any other information on our Website.

## Privacy Policy

Clearwind is committed to doing e-business with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls. We are also committed to providing better service to our customers. We adhere to the following policies with regards to your privacy.

## Credit Card Information

To purchase products from our Website, you may have to provide a credit card for billing purposes. We use 3rd party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services. We will use our best efforts to make sure that your credit card number is kept STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL by using only 3rd party billing services that use the latest security encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use. However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number.

## Use Of Cookies

Our Website may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of our site you have visited, so the next time you visit the site, those pages may be readily accessible. We also may use this information to better personalize the content that you see on our Website.

## Security Policy & User ID/Password

Our site utilizes various information security measures such as internet firewalls, an intrusion detection system, encrypted data transmission, and operating procedures to protect your personal data, accounts, passwords, etc. This information is kept completely separate and confidential; there is no chance of any other customer seeing your information unless you have given them your user ID and password. As such, you should protect your user ID and password and NOT share it with anyone. If you believe your user ID and password have been compromised, please contact our technical support department  
so they can issue you a new user ID/password.

## Information We Collect

In order to offer you meaningful products and services and for other reasons, we collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: Information you give us on applications or other forms OR Information about your transactions with us and our affiliates "Nonpublic personal information" is nonpublic information that is personally identifiable and obtained in connection with providing a product or service to you. It may include information about your account balance and payment history with us, and your purchase activity.

## Information Sharing

With the exception of sharing information with affiliates that assist us with billing you for your purchases from our Website, we do not share your information with any other parties.

## Your Acceptance of This Privacy Policy

This is our entire Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. You agree to it every time you use our Website.

## Questions About This Privacy Policy

Should you have a privacy question about our Website, please email our using our contact form.
